You think you've got me cornered, but
I've already implemented my tactics.
No!
What the!
I really hate to say it, but Okuyasu's
brother just about took me out for good.
Koichi, I think it's high time
we got the hell out of here.
Huh?
But what about the bow and arrow he had?
Where did it go?
Good memory.
Bastard must have hit it somewhere
after he dragged you up the stairs.
Don't tell me you wanna...
Yeah.
Hold off on looking for it.
If their dad bought this
place, he may still be around.
Plus, I'm too badly hurt
to be of much help to you.
Let's just leave it be for now.
No!
We can't just do nothing!
Look,
the only reason I'm alive right now is
because you healed my wounds with your stand.
But think about it.
If somebody else gets shot
with that bow and arrow,
Let's face it, they're probably gonna die!
Is that what you want?
You can stay here and rest up.
Don't worry about me.
I'll find it by myself.
And truth be told.
I'm not so sure their dad even
lives in this house anymore?.
I mean, if he was living here?
He would have come out by now, right?
He may not look it, but Koichi
has a hell of a lot of guts.
At least when things get
tough, or he's not in his head.
But that won't mean a thing if
we don't make it out of here.
We need to leave as fast as we can.
Hey!
Oh, it's you!
What, you trying to stop me?
Not a chance.
We're gonna snap that bow and arrow in
two, then say goodbye to this hellhole.
Together.
There's an attic.
The bow and arrow's probably up here.
There it is!
The bow and arrow!
And it's just hanging on the wall!
That doesn't sound good.
Something must be in there.
Well, at least it's
chained up, whatever it is.
You think it could be a dog?
Because it's definitely not a person.
Well, if it is, it sure isn't happy.
What are we supposed to do?
I'm too scared to think.
By asking me, I voted to
leave this house of horrors.
I know, but...
We can't just turn back now.
All right, Koichi,
on the count of three, I want you to bust
the door open with everything you've got.
That should scare it.
Then I'll run over as fast as I can
and break that bow and arrow in half.
You got it?
Yeah.
Let's go.
One, two, three!
What the hell?!
Koichi!
Help me! Wait a minute.
That thing is no stand.
It's a real hand attached
to a real funky-looking arm!
Help me, please!
Char!
Fuck!
I wasn't trying to sever it.
Hey, Koichi, what the hell is that thing?
I can't believe something like that
was living right under our noses.
Uh, gross.
So you found him.
That was never supposed to happen.
You again.
It's a long story, but he's our father.
If you can believe it and right
now he needs these more than you.
Why is he grabbing the bow and arrow?
It's imperative that I find
more stand users for my father.
So no one is getting these.
Come at me with all your might.
If you must, I'll protect
him until the bitter end.
So did a disease do this
to your dad? A disease.
You're joking.
Dad is an excellent
health minus the warts.
He even has a hearty appetite.
And all he does is moan.
It's safe to say he has
no idea I'm his son.
So you've been searching for a stand user
with the power to cure
your father to cure him.
What are you offering?
Because you're not needed.
You're wrong.
I've been searching for a stand
user who can kill my father.
But at this point, I
doubt it'll ever happen.
No matter what I do, Dad won't die.
I could bash his head in or chop
his body into a million tiny pieces.
Even slicing him to
ribbons won't kill him.
I just want to end his suffering.
As a kid, I swore to do everything
in my power to make that happen.
But I need the bow and arrow in order
to make good on my promise to him.
If I hand these over to you, dad
will be a freak for all eternity.
Suffering.
All because some bastard
named Dio decided to
implant cells in his skull and
make my dad a monster! Hold on.
Did you say Dio?
The guy from Mr.
Jotaro's story.
Indulge me by listening
to how things used to be.
Josuke Higashikata.
Although what I'm about to tell you
is related to your life as well.
Everything began 11 years ago.
1988 was the beginning of the end.
I was 7 that year and my
brother Okuyasu was just 4.
We were living in Tokyo during this time.
It was the middle of the bubble
economy and spirits were high.
Well, the spirits of
everyone except my father.
Mom fell sick and died.
When Dad's business went under, he
was buried under a mountain of debt.
He'd often beat us for no reason.
It was the walking definition of a loser.
That's when everything changed.
Out of the blue, a seemingly endless
supply of cash started rolling in.
And on top of that, there were
jewels and precious metals.
But Dad didn't have a job to speak of.
After some research,
I found out the truth.
My father had made a dark deal.
He sold his own soul to
a man by the name of Dio.
He became Dio's lackey for monetary gain.
Based on what I found out,
Dio's goal was to scour the globe
in search of potential stand users.
And somehow, he discovered my dad
had the capacity to manifest a stand.
However, to this day, I have no idea
what the nature of his stand is.
And then things changed again.
It's been ten years, but I
remember it like yesterday.
It was two in the afternoon.
I'd just come home from
a long day at school.
Okuyasu!
Did that bastard hit you again?
What's wrong with him?
No, he didn't.
Dio!
Dio is dead!
That must be the reason!
Dad?
I'll call an ambulance!
It's no use!
I'm not sick!
The flesh blood is ravaging my body!
This is the end! Dad!
After a year, he didn't know who we were.
The man had forgotten all
about his own children
and had become a muttering glob of flesh.
Dio used to implant his own cells
into the minds of those he distrusted
so he could manipulate his victims
in whatever way he saw fit.
And as you can guess, he implanted
one of those things into Dad.
For 10 years i threw myself into research
i studied stands i learned about jotaro In
my studies i learned of anyaba the hag and
obtained possession of
the bow and arrow But
in the process i slowly resigned myself to
the fact that dad would never recover from
The curse that plagued him my father had
already become one with
the immortal cells of dio
Now he spends his days
doing nothing but this.
It's infuriating to watch.
Every moment of every day
for the past ten years,
he's scratched around that
stupid box of rubbish.
If I confiscate it, he wails
and groans for days on end.
I'm sick of dealing with it.
Look at his putrid face.
Makes me disgusted with the
very idea of life itself.
I've told you over and
over, stop making a mess!
Though I've noticed, when I discipline
the bastard, he seems to hear me!
And he keeps rummaging in his own filth!
But I guess the swine can't help it!
Enough!
You're the one who needs to stop!
He's still your father, isn't he?
Yeah, you're right.
This man is my father, but in blood only.
The detestable thing I see before
me isn't the father I used to know.
This man sold his soul to Dio and
is living the life he created.
But I'm not totally without a heart.
Seeing my one and only father
like this is unbearable.
You don't know how it feels.
All I want to do is end his life and
finally free him from this suffering.
And by putting him out of his misery,
I'll be able to live my life again.
What did I say?
I've had just about enough of you!
Get out of the box right now!
Hey!
You've more than made your point!
Sorry, but I just can't let
you have this bow and arrow!
Not now or ever!
That works for me!
I'll just take that bow and arrow later!
But right now, my sights
are set on that box!
Wait, the box?
It was clear from the way he
was clutching those scraps
of paper that there was
something important about them.
Now it makes sense.
A family photo.
He knew what he was doing.
He hasn't been mindlessly rummaging
through that box for ten years.
He's had a purpose.
He was looking for the photo of
his sons when they were young.
It's true that he's not completely
aware of his surroundings.
But deep down, his
memories are still intact.
Memories of better days.
Give up on looking for a stand that kills,
because if you focus on
using one that heals instead,
Then I'm willing to help you.
But first you'll have to hand over that
bow and arrow, because they're history.
You're not planning to run, are you?
Bro, please.
Enough is enough.
Okuyasu, come on.
Let's end this already.
There's no point in fighting him, right?
So, you stuck around.
What do you say?
There's a chance that could
get better, couldn't he?
So what if he doesn't
look the way he used to?
That stuff doesn't really matter.
The important thing is, he'd
have his memories and soul.
Right?
Nokuyasu, the hell do
you think you're doing?
Bro.
Move it, Okuyasu!
Don't you see it's far too late for me
to just turn my back on the mission?
I've already slaughtered
countless people in this
town with the very bow
and arrow you're gripping!
Besides, as far as I'm concerned,
you're no longer my brother.
As such, I have no qualms about
killing you where you stand.
Bro...
Question.
Is there anyone else living here
besides you two and your dad?
Others?
No, it's just the three of us.
That's...
it's coming from the outlet.
Okuyasu, pull your head
out of your ass, you idiot!
No! It broke!
I'll be relieving you of this
bow and arrow, Keicho Nijimura!
You do still remember me, don't you?
Since you awakened my stand when
you shot me with this arrow!
I do, and you are an idiot!
You can't handle the bow and arrow!
Keicho Nijimura!
Stands are a manifestation of the soul!
I've matured since you told me that!
But let me guess, you weren't
expecting my stand, Chili Pepper,
to evolve to this degree!
War's company, attack!
No more words!
Hey, is that electricity?
Okuyasu's brother is turning into it!
And so is the bow and arrow!
No!
No! Get back!
Don't touch me!
You'll get sucked into!
Big bro...
This isn't good!
All that work!
And he's stealing the bow and arrow!
Okuyasu, I knew you'd find
a way to screw me over.
Ever since we were kids,
you've always held me back.
It broke!
Josuke!
There's no doubt in my mind that a stand
user was watching us from that window.
Did you recognize that
stand back there, Okuyasu?
I didn't.
Bro was the one who found the STAND users,
and when he did, he didn't
tell me a lot about them.
Josuke, look! It's...
Okuyasu.
Bro, I knew it was only a matter
of time before this happened.
I knew all the bad things he did in
his life would catch up to him one day.
But still, in the end, my brother!
My brother used his dying moments
to save my life, didn't he?
Josuke, you saw it, right?
Yeah, I couldn't have said it better.
Whatever is false, your
brother saved your life.
Would this happen to be Jotaro Kujo?
I don't recognize your voice.
Who is this and what do you want from me?
The who doesn't matter, Jotaro Kujo.
But as for what I want, I'm kindly
asking you to get the hell out of Morioh.
Now let me see if I've got this straight.
A complete stranger calls and
wants me to just up and leave town.
What would you do if the
situation was reversed?
Doesn't matter since I
have the bow and arrow.
That's right.
I took it from Keicho
Nijimura after I killed him.
and I don't mind getting
rid of you either.
I've heard all about you, Jotaro,
that you have the ability to
stop time for one or two seconds.
But since you're such a tough guy,
I thought I'd take a shot at
convincing you over the phone first.
Are you a stand user too?
What do you want with the bow and arrow?
I don't mean to cause you any trouble,
if that's what you're implying.
And as long as Josuke Higashikata
minds his own business,
I won't lay a finger on him either.
I haven't had this stand
ability for too long,
so my only priority right now
is to have a little fun I've had
enough of dealing with mundane things
like entrance exams and resumes.
So you're a student, huh?
What difference does that make? Listen,
if you wear out your welcome,
I'll kill you and Josuke
in ways that'll haunt you
How many other stand users
are there in this town?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Here we go again.
Keicho Nijimura was buried in Kunimi
Peak Cemetery, west of Morioh.
However, the bow and
arrow remains missing.
For Okuyasu Nijimura, it was time to step
up and look after his father for a while.
end.
Josuke, can you get that?
Good morning.
Hey, Josuke!
Time to go to school, buddy!
Huh?
Starting today, the two of us are
going to be going to the same school.
Even so, that doesn't mean
you have to come and get me.
This isn't elementary school.
No way!
You know, I never realized your house
and my house were so close together.
Yeah, shocking.
But like I said, you don't
need to walk me to school.
Come on!
You don't want us to be late!
Hey there!
Are you one of Josuke's friends?
Hi!
I'm Okuyasu Nijimura!
Come on in and have some coffee
while he finishes getting ready.
Wow, really?
Don't mind if I do!
Have you noticed that
your mom's kinda hot?
I'm right behind ya!
A comedian.
Just great.
What have I done?
Oh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you, but ooh,
I'm trying to find you.